

Mohd Amir Amzar bin Sauli

Address: Lot 2052, Kampung Paloh Rambai, Batu 11, 16450 Ketereh, Kelantan.

Phone: 013-5877825

Email: amiramzar420@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

OBJECTIVE

To fully utilize my skills and knowledge in information technology to complete task within given time. Experienced in website development with knowledge and proficiency, as well as strong skills and ability in writing clean and efficient code. I am a fast learner and can work independently as well as work in team, willing to learn new skills and can start from any level of position.

EXPERIENCE

NU VENTURE RESOURCE SDN BHD

General Administration – Contract (FEB 2019 – JULY 2019)

- Responsible to assist the director on any task assigned.
- Become a driver to the director when needed to go to some places.
- Support the project manager during training session.
- Learning on developing mobile application using Basic4Android.
- Learn to use SQLite on android development.

2EN APPS SDN BHD

Web Developer – Intern (JULY 2018 - JAN 2019)

- Work with senior developer to develop and manage the system for corporate clients.
- Getting used with the LARAVEL framework all the way on developing the system.
- Complete development task for front end and as well as challenging back end development.
- Getting involved in database integration on several database server on such as PostgreSQL and Sybase.
- Experienced in carry out assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Joined meeting session with the clients to learn about the development of project scopes.
- Assist in training session for the user to understand on the system.
- Assist in making documentation of User Requirement Specification (URS).

STEELCASE(M) SDN BHD

Store Keeper – Part Time (JUN 2017 – AUG 2017)

- Responsible to manage the quantity and quality of the raw materials always updated in the system.
- Responsible in sending the raw materials to the production area.
- Must keep the arrangement of the raw materials on the right places and keep the area clean and tidy.

EDUCATION

INTERNATIONAL ISLAMIC UNIVERSITY MALAYSIA (IIUM), GOMBAK

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (HONORS)

• Final Year Project Title: Web-Based Risk Assessment for Information Security

CENTRE FOR FOUNDATION STUDIES IIUM, PETALING JAYA

FOUNDATION IN ENGINEERING AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

MARA JUNIOR SCIENCE COLLEGE KUBANG PASU, JITRA, KEDAH

SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA (SPM)

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- PHP
- HTML
- SQL
- Android Development
- LARAVEL
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Microsoft Office

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Malaysia (written, spoken)

• English (written, spoken)

Native

Moderate

REFERENCES

MR. NUZUL HAYAT BIN ARBAIN – Supervisor internship

Title: Director, 2en Apps Sdn. Bhd.

Phone: 019-2206871

Email: hayat@2enapps.com

Address: Suite 19/2A Jln UP 1/2, Ukay Perdana Business Park, Ampang, Selangor.

DR. NOOR HAYANI BINTI ABDUL RAHIM – Lecturer

Title: Assistant Professor IIUM

Phone: 013-4448283

Email: noorhayani@iium.edu.my

Address: Department of Information System, International Islamic University Malaysia,

Kuala Lumpur.